var mathdata = {
  "total_size": 4,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question":
          "In an Arithmetic Progression, if a = 28, d = -4, n = 7, then an is:",
      "option1": "4",
      "option2": " 5",
      "option3": "3",
      "option4": "7",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "11th term of the A.P. -3, -1/2, 2 …. Is",
      "option1": "28",
      "option2": "22",
      "option3": "-48",
      "option4": "-38",
      "ans": "b",
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "The pairs of equations x+2y-5 = 0 and -4x-8y+20=0 have?",
      "option1": "Unique solution",
      "option2": "Exactly two solutions",
      "option3": "Infinitely many solutions",
      "option4": "No solution",
      "ans": "c",
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question":
          "If a pair of linear equations is consistent, then the lines are?",
      "option1": "Parallel",
      "option2": "Always coincident",
      "option3": "Always intersecting",
      "option4": "Intersecting coincident",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question":
          "If a pair of linear equations is consistent, then the lines are:",
      "option1": "4/15",
      "option2": "5/14",
      "option3": "4/5",
      "option4": "5/4",
      "ans": "b",
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question":
          "one equation of a pair of dependent linear equations is -3x+5y-2=0. The second equation will be?",
      "option1": "-6x+10y-4=0",
      "option2": "6x-10y-4=0",
      "option3": "6x+10y-4=0",
      "option4": "-6x+10y+4=0",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "The solution of the equations x-y=2 and x+y=4 is:",
      "option1": "3 and 1",
      "option2": "5 and 4",
      "option3": "-1 and 2",
      "option4": "3 and 6",
      "ans": "a",
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question":
          "The pair of equations x = a and y = b graphically represents lines which are:",
      "option1": "parallel",
      "option2": "intersecting at (b, a)",
      "option3": "coincident",
      "option4": "intersecting at (a, b)",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question":
          "The pair of equations x + 2y + 5 = 0 and –3x – 6y + 1 = 0 have:",
      "option1": "a unique solution",
      "option2": "exactly two solutions",
      "option3": "many solutions",
      "option4": "no solution",
      "ans": "d",
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question":
          "The value of c for which the pair of equations cx – y = 2 and 6x – 2y = 3 will have infinitely many solutions is:",
      "option1": "3",
      "option2": "-3",
      "option3": "-12",
      "option4": "no value",
      "ans": "d",
    },
  ]
};
